(
"ai_sub_version": "1.12.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "h264_qsv"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Liminal #桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026
Liminal #Nene Momosuzu Birthday Live 2026
一斉のーで鳴り響いたスタートの合図
All at once, the starting signal rang out
なぞって 線で結んだ世界 色付けてく
Tracing the connected lines, coloring in the world
ここから
From here
かくれんぼ / 作詞・作曲：TKT
Kakurenbo / Lyrics & Composition: TKT
物心がつく頃
Around the time I became aware of the world
すでにここにあった
It was already here
今日は夕日が沈むと共に蘇る
Today, as the sun sets, it comes back to life
古ぼけた絵本を取り出して
Taking out an old, worn-out picture book
落書きの中に一つの答えを見つけた
I found a single answer amidst the scribbles
自分の価値に目を疑って
Doubting my own worth
どこまでだって落ちて行けるの
How far down can I keep falling?
どこか遠くに消えてしまいたい
I want to disappear somewhere far away
こんな世界じゃ僕は要らない
In a world like this, I am not needed
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun
いっせーので声を上げて
On the count of three, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づく
Realizing the length of my own shadow
もうそんな時間だ
It's already that time
一等星が顔を出した
The first-magnitude star has shown its face
届きそうで手を伸ばした
It looked reachable, so I reached out my hand
次は僕についてきなよと
Saying "Follow me next time"
暗闇でも
Even in the darkness
もういいかい まだだよ
"Are you ready?" "Not yet."
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has started to rise
もういいかい まだだよ
"Are you ready?" "Not yet."
色付けてく ここから
Coloring it in, starting from here
10年後の僕らは
Ten years from now, we are...
すれ違いばかりで
...just passing each other by
幻想に想いを馳せては
Thinking of illusions...
戻れない
...we can't go back
そう思い込んだ
That's what I convinced myself
くたびれた心に追い討ちを
Striking a blow to my worn-out heart
あの頃と変わらない夕日も
Even the sunset that hasn't changed since back then...
なんとも思わない
...I don't feel anything about it
自分を信じ歩いてければ
If I could just believe in myself and keep walking...
どこまでだって登れるのにな
...I could climb anywhere, I suppose
カット跨ぐその空白に
In that blank space spanning the cut
大切なもの見落としている
I'm overlooking something important
見つけられないと
"I can't find it,"
泣き喚く君へ
...to you, who are crying and screaming
いっせーので声を上げて
On the count of three, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づく
Realizing the length of my own shadow
もうそんな時間だ
It's already that time
一等賞で駆け抜ける君
You, running through in first place
くっついてただけの僕でも
Even I, who was just sticking to you
君の前を歩けるかな
I wonder if I can walk in front of you
こんな頼りない僕でも
Even a unreliable person like me
空っぽの箱は埃を
The empty box...
被ったまま無くした
...was lost while covered in dust
鍵はずっと君の
The key was always...
ポケットの中にあった
...inside your pocket
散らばってた全てが
Everything that was scattered...
今ひとつに重なる
...now overlaps into one
手を取り始めよう
Let's take hands and begin
僕たちの物語
Our story
一度は諦めた
The one we gave up on once
思い出の続きを
The continuation of our memories
いつから忘れて
Since when have we...
しまっていたのかな
...forgotten about it?
散らばってた全てが
Everything that was scattered...
愛しくて
It's so dear
今ひとつに重なる
...now overlaps into one
掛け声はいつも
The shout is always...
いっせーので声を上げて
On the count of three, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づく
Realizing the length of my own shadow
もうそんな時間だ
It's already that time
一等星が顔を出した
The first-magnitude star has shown its face
届きそうで手を伸ばした
It looked reachable, so I reached out my hand
次は僕についてきなよと
Saying "Follow me next time"
暗闇でも
Even in the darkness
もういいかい まだだよ
"Are you ready?" "Not yet."
泣きじゃくった声で
With a sobbing voice
もういいかい まだだよ
"Are you ready?" "Not yet."
笑う君が見えた
I saw you laughing
もういいかい まだだよ
"Are you ready?" "Not yet."
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has started to rise
もういいかい
"Are you ready?"
もういいよ
"I'm ready."
色付けてく ここから
Coloring it in, starting from here
鉛の空 重く垂れ込み
The leaden sky hangs heavy and low.
真白に澱んだ 太陽が砕けて
The sun, stagnated in pure white, shatters.
耳鳴りを 尖らせる
Sharpening the ringing in my ears.
ヒュルリヒュルリ 低いツバメが
Hyururi, hyururi, the low-flying swallows,
8の字なぞって ビルの谷をかける
Trace a figure eight and dash through the valley of buildings.
もうじきに
Very soon,
夕立が来る
The evening shower will come.
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On the cloudy road, having forgotten her umbrella,
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてるの
She walks, frightened of the rain.
って僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
And I, too, dangling my cowardice,
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky.
あちらこちら 暗躍は上手
Here and there, skilled in secret maneuvers.
珈琲屋に寄って 一休み決めたら
Stopping by the coffee shop, once we decide to take a break,
帰れない
We can't go home.
帰らない
We won't go home.
曇天の道を ぶらりぶらぶら
Aimlessly wandering the cloudy road,
歩く二人は 足軽のごとく
The two walking are like foot soldiers.
危険好きの 誰かのふりをする
Pretending to be someone who loves danger,
小心者共
We are just cowards.
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On the cloudy road, having forgotten her umbrella,
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてるの
She walks, frightened of the rain.
って僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
And I, too, dangling my cowardice,
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky.
混同いて育つもの なんだなんだろ
What is it that grows when confused? What could it be?
ワンバンコ！ワンバンコ！
Good evening! Good evening!
Never Never Give Up!
ワンバンコ！ワンバンコ！
Good evening! Good evening!
Never Give Up!
運営さん、なんか放送エコが切れてるかもしれないとのことで
Management-san, apparently the broadcast echo might be cut off,
確認お願いします！
so please check it!
出会いましては簡単すぎるよ
Meeting you is too simple.
最初に決めた答えは一つ
The answer I decided at the start is one.
ときめきましたか 合格しますか
Did your heart flutter? Do I pass?
恋も勝負も慌てない
I won't rush in love or in battle.
コツコツコツと徹夜にため息
Sighing at the all-nighter, tapping away steadily.
私の中見て 偏差値ドリーマー
Look inside me, I'm a Deviation Score Dreamer.
思うことみな叶えばいいな
I wish everything I think of would come true.
人の世界は気にしない
I don't care about other people's worlds.
Perfect-area complete!
絶対ここで待ってるんだ
I'm definitely waiting right here.
Perfect-area 望む声が
Perfect-area, the wishing voices,
聞こえるよ
I can hear them.
Ah! Why? 止まらない
Ah! Why? It won't stop.
すれ違い
Passing each other by.
私が想定外なら
If I am unexpected,
友達かい？ 友達です
Are we friends? We are friends.
悲しき0点だね
That's a sad zero score.
No! やり直し
No! Start over.
書き直し
Rewrite it.
本気でワンチャン・プリーズ
Seriously, one chance please.
今より素敵な未来があるのに
Even though there's a future more wonderful than now.
今より素敵に My Life My Life
Make my life more wonderful than now, My Life.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんなもありがとう！
Thank you everyone too!
否　否　イヤ
No, no, no way.
さりげなく聞いてみた
I tried asking casually.
私の勉強不足で
Due to my lack of study,
可能性ありますか？
is there any possibility?
試験はなんてかな？
I wonder what the test will be?
誰だって君だって
Anyone, even you,
間に合う気は一緒
we share the feeling of making it in time.
これから始まる季節に挨拶
Greetings to the season starting now.
これから始める My Life My Life My Life
Starting from now, My Life, My Life, My Life.
気がついた時には
When I realized it,
生まれてた なぜだろう
it had been born, I wonder why.
さあね
Who knows?
意識はもう育ちつつあるよ
Consciousness is already growing.
強く強くね
Strongly, strongly.
わい！ 止まらないこの気持ち
Yay! This feeling won't stop.
私の勉強不足で
Due to my lack of study,
可能性ありますか？
is there any possibility?
それとも例外かな？
Or is it an exception?
Non! やり残し書き残し
Non! Left undone, left unwritten.
本気でワンワンジャンプ
Seriously One-One-Jump.
今より素敵な未来があるから
Because there is a future more wonderful than now,
今より素敵に My Life My Life My Life
more wonderful than now, My Life, My Life, My Life.
はい！ということで始まりました！
Yes! So, it has begun!
2026 桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ YAY!
2026 Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live YAY!
みんなコメントも見えてるよ ありがとう！
I can see everyone's comments too, thank you!
エコー気づいてくれた人ありがとう
Thanks to those who noticed the echo.
ねねこうないと死んじゃう病気だから
Because Nene has a sickness where she dies if it's not like this.
はいということで今回のハッシュタグはこちら
Okay, so, here is this time's hashtag.
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 です
It's #MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026.
今ねエゴサの機能がちょっとバグっちゃってるんで
Right now the ego-search function is bugging out a bit,
こっちでツイートしてくれたらめっちゃ嬉しいです
so I'd be super happy if you tweeted with this one.
よろしくお願いします
Please and thank you!
今日はね 超重大告知があるので
There is a super important announcement today,
最後まで楽しんでいってください
so please enjoy it until the end.
さあ今 3曲をお聴きいただいたんですけど
So, you've just listened to three songs,
ねねの好きな曲
Nene's favorite songs...
銀魂
Gintama,
バカテス
BakaTest,
っていう感じでね もうねねの好きな曲しかない3曲をやりましたけど
like that, I did three songs that are nothing but Nene's favorites, but...
3曲目に一番... 歌がキツイの持ってきちゃって
I brought the one that's hardest to sing for the third song,
ゼハゼハでございます
and I am panting.
ということでここからはゲストパート入っていきます
So, from here we will enter the guest part.
それでは VTR Let's Go!
Alright then, VTR Let's Go!
噛みしめたいんだ
I want to reflect on it.
驚かしたいんだ
I want to surprise you,
今は我慢しよ
but let's hold back for now.
Coolish Walk
明調子が第一です
Being in top form comes first.
はやる心を抑えて
Suppressing my eager heart,
今日は識人になりましょう
let's be knowledgeable people today.
やっぱ人なら救われる
After all, if you're human, you can be saved.
青い二人のヘブン
The blue heaven of us two.
恋のなる夢は Rare
Dreams where love grows are Rare.
愉快 特盛の脳
A pleasant, extra-large brain.
トレースして
Trace it.
空を駆け回りたい
I want to run around the sky.
揺れる想いの下
Beneath swaying thoughts,
ガーリックには
in the garlic...
恋のインタだけ膨らんでる
only the love inter is swelling.
すごいメニューを作る
Making an amazing menu,
と野望なら
if that's the ambition,
まともにフルーツ育みましょう
let's properly grow fruits.
高まりたいんだ
I want to rise up.
味わいたいんだ
I want to taste it.
雄叫びたいんだ
I want to shout.
そんな夢を見て
Dreaming such a dream,
Coolish Walk
太鼓判は期限です
The seal of approval is the deadline.
むかつく午後は深呼吸
Deep breaths for an annoying afternoon.
優雅な音 奏でましょう
Let's play an elegant sound.
キレる人は
Those who get angry
余ってる
are left over.
強くなさそうな 君は
You, who don't seem strong...
壊れそうな 逃げる
Fragile, running away...
ループする愛
...from this looping love.
イメージして 街を
Visualize it, the town...
飛び跳ねよう
Let's jump around!
すまし顔で無視の
With a straight face, ignoring...
ほっぺたに
...on your cheek.
意外なお願いが 詰まってる
It's packed with unexpected requests.
誰も知らないストーリー
A story no one knows.
恐れないで
Don't be afraid.
まっすぐゴールを 突き詰めましょ
Let's pursue the goal straight on!
Pan Pan Pan...
遠いあこがれ ヘブン
Distant longing, Heaven.
時々見失う ティア
Sometimes losing sight, Tear.
胸の涙のカケラ
Fragments of tears in my heart...
イレースしよ
Let's erase them.
憂鬱 片付けよう
Let's tidy up the melancholy.
揺れる思いの 下の果肉には
In the fruit flesh beneath wavering thoughts,
恋の美味しさだけ 膨らんでる
Only the deliciousness of love is swelling up.
すごいメニュー作る と野望なら
If the ambition is to create an amazing menu,
魔王にフルーツ 育みましょ
Let's nurture fruits for the Demon King.
抱きしめたいんだ
I want to hug you!
パンパンパン
Pan Pan Pan
噛み締めたいんだ
I want to savor it!
モグモグ
Munch munch
驚かしたいんだ
I want to surprise you!
今我慢しよ
Let's endure for now.
修行しよ
Let's train!
気合いしよ Coolish Walk
Let's get fired up! Coolish Walk!
口づけを かわした日は
The day we exchanged a kiss,
ママの顔さえも 見れなかった
I couldn't even look at Mama's face.
ポケットの コイン集めて
Gathering coins from the pocket,
ひとつずつ夢を 数えたね
We counted our dreams one by one, didn't we?
ほらあれは 2人の隠れ家
Look, that's our hideout.
秘密のメモリー
Secret memory.
どこで壊れたの
Where did it break?
Oh フレンズ
Oh Friends.
うつむく日は みつめあって
On days we looked down, we stared at each other.
指をつないだら
When we held hands,
Oh フレンズ
Oh Friends.
時が止まる 気がした
I felt like time stopped.
ねえ君は 覚えている
Hey, do you remember?
夕映えに よく似合うあの曲
That song that suits the sunset well.
黙り込む 君がいつも
You, who always fell silent...
悲しくて 口ずさんだのに
...hummed it because you were sad.
今時は流れて セピアに染まるメロディー
Now time flows, the melody dyed in sepia.
二度と戻れない
We can never go back again.
Oh フレンズ
Oh Friends.
他人よりも 遠く見えて
You look more distant than a stranger.
いつも走ってた
We were always running.
Oh フレンズ
Oh Friends.
あの瞳が 愛しい
I miss those eyes.
どこで壊れたの
Where did it break?
oh フレンズ
oh Friends
うつむく日は
On days when we look down,
みつめあって
we gaze at each other.
指を繋いだら
If we link our fingers,
oh フレンズ
oh Friends
時が止まる
I felt like time
気がした
stopped moving.
二度と戻れない
We can never go back,
oh フレンズ
oh Friends
他人よりも
You look more distant
遠く見えて
than a stranger.
いつも走ってた
We were always running,
oh フレンズ
oh Friends
あの瞳が
Those eyes
愛しい
are so dear to me.
Chu Chu Yeah!
Please me!
Without you!
あぁなんてことだ
Ah, what a mess,
些細な過ちだ
just a trivial mistake.
自分のことに
Grumbling on and on
タラタラ文句を垂れてる
about myself.
堂々巡りをしてる
Going around in circles,
逃げ切ったっていいでしょ
it's okay to run away, right?
だけどなんだか
But somehow,
気まぐれモードになり
I'm in a whimsical mode,
そんな気分になっちゃって
that's just how I feel now.
始まりはそんな風で
That's how it all started,
つまりはらしくないようで
in short, it seems unlike me.
でも今 扉開けて
But now, open the door,
ほら
look,
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear the voice,
さあ 行こう
come on, let's go.
どこへでも
Anywhere.
僕は君の
I will become
翼に
your wings,
なれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to be.
Please stay with me
どんな試練も
I'm not afraid
怖くない
of any trial,
その魔法があるから
because I have that magic.
初めて出会う
To the world we meet
世界に
for the first time,
花束を贈ろう
let's send a bouquet.
Made in society
ただこの瞬間
We are connected
結ばれるよ
in this moment.
ちぐはぐな
An awkward
コミュニケーション？
communication?
でも別に
But I don't
構わない
really mind.
明日から
If it's peaceful
平和なら
from tomorrow.
Chu Chu Yeah!
Without you!
あぁどうしてまた
Ah, why can't I
素直になれなくて
be honest again?
自分のことで
About myself,
チュルル チュル チュルリラ
chururu churu chururira.
ギヤはそのままで
Keep the gear as is,
スピード上げて行こう
let's speed up.
だけどなんだか
But somehow,
黄昏モードになり
I'm in a twilight mode,
いつか思い出して
someday remember this.
一人でいても
I don't dislike
嫌じゃない
being alone,
誰にも
I don't need to
頼らなくてもいい
rely on anyone.
でも扉の向こう
But it's noisy
騒がしい
on the other side of the door.
声が聞きたいよ
I want to hear your voice,
今 行こう
now let's go.
どこへでも
Anywhere.
僕は君を
I'll carry you
背中に
on my back
乗せて空を舞うよ
and fly through the sky.
Please fly with me
いつか心が
Even if our hearts
離れても
drift apart someday,
その時は笑ってね
smile when that time comes.
守りたい
To this world
この世界に
I want to protect,
青空のラプソディ
a Blue Sky Rhapsody.
Make me smile &
ただいつまでも
Just keep playing it
奏でていてよ
forever.
凸凹な
An uneven
コンビネーション？
combination?
でも別に
But it's
大丈夫さ
totally fine.
明日はまた
Tomorrow will be
平和な
peaceful again.
ほんの小さな
A tiny little
傷を
scratch,
太陽に
expose it
晒して
to the sun.
分け合ったよ
I shared it
君と
with you.
痛みは熱さの中に
The pain melts
溶けてく
into the heat.
Chu Chu Yeah!
息もできず
We bounce without
弾く僕ら
being able to breathe.
手を叩いて
Clap your hands.
何が何でも
No matter what,
弾く二人
we bounce together.
手と手を繋ごう僕ら
Let's hold hands, us.
手を叩いて
Clap your hands.
無限のリズムではしゃぐんだ
Frolic with infinite rhythm.
どこまでも僕は君の
I have the courage to become
翼になれる勇気があるよ
your wings anywhere.
どんな試練も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any trial,
その魔法があるから
because I have that magic.
君と出会い世界は
When I met you, the world
花束に溢れた
was filled with bouquets.
ただその瞬間が全てだよ
Just that moment is everything.
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーションでも別に構わない
I don't mind if our communication is mismatched.
明日が平和なら
As long as tomorrow is peaceful.
With me
Chu Chu Yeah!
はぁー！はい！
Haa! Yes!
やりきったー！
We did it!
やりきりましたー！
ねね間違えたけど...
Nene made a mistake but...
多分気付かれてないから大丈夫！
They probably didn't notice so it's fine!
私も間違えました！
I also made a mistake!
あれ？
Huh?
みんな大丈夫！？
Is everyone okay!?
バレてないバレてない！
Not exposed, not exposed!
大丈夫！
It's fine!
えーというわけで今日はねねの誕生日記念ライブに
So, today for Nene's birthday memorial live,
可愛い後輩二人に来てもらいましたー！
I got two cute juniors to come!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you!
ねね先輩おめでとう！
Nene-senpai, congratulations!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
リアナス？
Realize?
リオナス？
Rionasu?
やります？
Shall we do it?
やる...？
Do it...?
やっぱなんかちょっと... 求められてる？
As expected... are we being sought after?
曲より動いてるから
We're moving more than the song requires.
今めっちゃ息切れしましたよ
I'm totally out of breath now!
でも嬉しいです呼んでいただいて！
But I'm happy you invited us!
ねーありがとう！
Yeah, thanks!
フログロのライブ見てから
After watching Flow Glow's live,
完成度が高すぎて
the perfection was too high.
一旦呼ぼうと思ったけど
I thought about calling you once but,
やっぱまた辞めようかなって
I thought I should stop again.
なんでよ！
Why!
いいじゃん！一緒に出来ないと思ったけど
It's fine! I thought I couldn't do it with you,
なんでよー！
Why!
今回頑張っちゃいました
but I did my best this time!
楽しかったねー
It was fun.
デビューしてからの目標が
My goal since debut was
先輩と一緒にステージで歌って踊ることやったから
to sing and dance on stage with Senpai.
それが今日叶ったんです
That came true today.
やったー！
Yay!
良かったねぇ
That's great!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
初めての3D！
First 3D!
やったー！
Yay!
いぇーい！
Yeah!
え、じゃあ最後可愛くポーズ決めて
Well then, finally strike a cute pose,
写真撮って終わりにしようかなと思います
let's take a photo and end it.
全力でみんなそれぞれ可愛いポーズね！
Everyone do their own cute pose with full power!
フリじゃないよ！
It's not a setup!
可愛くね！
Cute, okay!
可愛く！
Cute!
分かった！
Got it!
せーの！
Ready, set!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あれ？
Huh?
ちょ、待って！
Wait a sec!
裏切ったな！
You betrayed us!
無口なハート開いたら
If you open your silent heart,
いつも声合わせて
Always unison our voices.
キラキラしている自分を
Let's grab the sparkling
掴もう大好きなことしよう
versions of ourselves, let's do what we love.
勝ちが負けたなんて関係ないと思い
Winning or losing doesn't matter.
手と手繋いで Hey Jump!
Hold hands and Hey Jump!
パーティを始める
Start the party.
Hey let's go party time
Let's dance 1, 2, 3 Realize!
もっとずっとみんなで
More and forever, with everyone,
絶対諦めたくないから
because I definitely don't want to give up.
Let's dream do my best
明日はきっと輝いている
Tomorrow will surely be shining.
力合わせてときめき探してく
Combine our strength and search for excitement.
掴み取ろうプリパラ
Let's grab it, PriPara.
問題ないない！なんてことない！ビビってないじゃない
No problem, no way! Nothing to it! I'm not scared at all!
さあ勇気を出して
Come on, show some courage!
Hey Clap！ ほら夢が始まる
Hey Clap! Look, the dream is beginning!
Realize！ Dream comes true！
Realize! Dream comes true!
Let's dance！ Dance with me！ 未来へ
Let's dance! Dance with me! To the future!
そうずっとみんなで
Yes, always together with everyone.
絶対手放したくないから
Because I absolutely don't want to let go.
Let's sing！ Sing my phase！
Let's sing! Sing my phase!
明日はもっと輝いてる
Tomorrow will be shining even more.
希望を掲げて
Raise your hopes high!
ドキドキ探してく
Go search for the excitement.
誰のものプリパラ
Who does PriPara belong to?
うまくいかないとか
Things not going well...
すれ違いばかりで
Just passing each other by...
ダメになりそうな時は一緒に
When it feels like it's all going wrong, let's be together.
二つ折りの夢を叶えよう
Let's make our two-fold dream come true.
笑顔
A smile...
受け取ろう
...let's receive it!
そう一緒に歌いたい
Yes, I want to sing together.
ねえ一緒に踊りたい
Hey, I want to dance together.
絶対諦めないよ
I definitely won't give up!
Let's go!
Let's dance！ One, Two, Three！ 未来へ
Let's dance! One, Two, Three! To the future!
そうずっとみんなで
Yes, always together with everyone.
絶対諦めたくないから
Because I absolutely don't want to give up.
Let's sing！ Do my best！
Let's sing! Do my best!
明日はきっと輝いてる
Tomorrow will surely be shining.
力を合わせて
Combine our strength...
ときめき探してく
...and go search for the excitement.
つかみとろう プリパラ
Let's grab it, PriPara!
はーい！おけおけ！
Haaai! Okay, okay!
Let's Dance！
Let's Dance!
ちょっと待って！一旦！
Wait a minute! Just a sec!
ねね！
Nene!
お疲れ！おめでとう！
Good work! Congratulations!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ちょっとね、コメントと30秒くらい差があるんだって
Hold on, they say there's about a 30-second lag with the comments.
あ、そうなの？
Oh, is that so?
大丈夫、また後で
It's fine, we'll check later.
お邪魔します！
Excuse us!
いやマジでさ、Realize！
No seriously, Realize!
いや本当にこのゆくあんさんの…
No really, this Yukuan-san's...
メン限でいい？もうメン限にしよう
Can we save this for members-only? Let's make it members-only.
メン限で話そう！あとであるから
Let's talk in members-only! We have that later.
おまるんと飛べるようになったの！
I became able to fly with Omarun!
見てねー！
Watch this!
面白いポーズ！
Funny pose!
３、２、１…
3, 2, 1...
うわあああ！
Uwaaaaah!
無理無理無理！
No way, no way, no way!
提案です！あたし推し変ない？
Here's a proposal! You won't change your oshi, right?
なんてね！
Just kidding!
君専用…
Dedicated to you...
君専用！
Just for you!
トーストかじって
Biting on toast,
交差点でぶつかる
Bumping into someone at the intersection.
そういうんじゃないけど
It's not really like that, but...
予感はしてたよ
I had a premonition.
きっとね運命だね
Surely, it's fate, right?
会えるって信じてた
I believed we would meet.
君専用の笑顔 スタンバイOK！
A smile just for you, standby OK!
愚痴が出たり
Complaining sometimes...
ため息ついたり
...or sighing.
あるよね わかるよ
It happens, I understand.
君が寂しくて泣いてるなら
If you are lonely and crying,
いらだちでたまらないなら
If the frustration is unbearable,
あたしの出番だな
It's my turn!
その手をさあもっと手繰り寄せて
Come on, pull that hand closer.
連れてくよ
I'll take you with me!
ようこそ無敵なテーマパーク
Welcome to the invincible theme park!
思い出全部
All your memories...
忘れちゃえ
...just forget them!
とりあえずは
For now...
あたしだけ見て
...look only at me.
底なしの沼だぞ
It's a bottomless swamp, you know.
ちょっと考えられないくらい
To the point you can't even think straight,
愛をあげる
I'll give you love.
君が好きだ
I love you!
提案です！あたし推し変ない？
Here's a proposal! You won't change your oshi, right?
なんてね！
Just kidding!
どうやらフラグはまだ立っていないみたいだ
It seems the flag hasn't been raised yet.
困難も気にしない
I don't care about the hardships.
一直線に奮え
Tremble in a straight line.
きっとね安定だね
It's surely stable, isn't it?
お決まりのツーショ
The usual two-shot.
二人きりの空間スタンバイOK
A space for just the two of us, standby OK.
舞い上がっちゃって
Soaring high,
後で反省会
we'll have a reflection meeting later.
あるよねわかるよ
That happens, I understand.
脳内占拠して眠れないなら
If I occupy your brain and you can't sleep,
そわそわしてたまらないなら
if you're fidgeting and can't stand it,
いつだっておいでよ
come over anytime.
少しずつ積み上げていこう
Let's build it up little by little.
ようこそ無限のパラダイム
Welcome to the infinite paradigm.
もういっそずっと一緒にいよう
Let's just stay together forever.
とことんまで笑っていてね
Keep laughing until the very end.
もっと信じて欲しいんだぞ
I want you to believe in me more.
ちょっと掴んだチャンスの裾
The hem of the chance I just grabbed,
最上級をプレゼントしよう
I'll present you with the highest quality.
疑うなんかいなくてもいいよ
You don't need to have any doubts.
ただ楽しいを続けよう
Let's just keep having fun.
繋いだ今日が明日になってくんだ
The today we connected will become tomorrow.
ヨーソロー全速前進で
Aye aye! Full speed ahead!
とんでもない景色見に行こう
Let's go see some incredible scenery.
乗りかかってる
You're already on board,
自覚あるでしょ
you realize that, right?
そんじょそこらの遊びじゃ
With just run-of-the-mill play,
もう満足できないくらい
I can't be satisfied anymore.
夢中になれる
I can become engrossed,
夢中にさせる
I'll make you engrossed.
ようこそ無敵なテーマパーク
Welcome to the invincible theme park.
もういっそ全部忘れちゃえ
Just forget everything already.
リア充エースはあたしだけ見て
Real life ace, look only at me.
底なしの沼だぞ
It's a bottomless swamp.
ちょっと考えられないくらい
So much you can't even think.
愛をあげる
I'll give you love.
君が好きだ
I like you.
時間なんて関係ないさ
Time doesn't matter.
今だってほら笑ってるじゃん
See, you're smiling right now.
提案です
I have a proposal.
あたし始めない？
Won't you start 'me'?
なんてね
Just kidding.
突然降る夕立 ああ傘もないやいや
Sudden evening shower, ah, I don't even have an umbrella.
空のご機嫌なんか知らない
I don't care about the sky's mood.
季節の変わり目の服は何着りゃいいんだろう
I wonder what I should wear when the seasons change.
春と秋どこいっちゃったんだよ
Where did spring and autumn go?
息もできない
I can't even breathe.
情報の圧力
The pressure of information.
めまいの螺旋だ
It's a spiral of dizziness.
私はどこにいる
Where am I?
こんなにこんなに息の音がするのに
Even though I can hear my breathing so loud,
変だね 世界の音がしない
it's strange, there's no sound from the world.
足りない足りない
Not enough, not enough.
誰にも気づかれない
Unnoticed by anyone.
殴り書きみたいな音 出せない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed a sound like scribbling without being able to let it out.
ありのままなんて誰に見せるんだ
Who am I supposed to show my true self to?
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
Stupid me just sings.
ぶちまけちゃおうか
Shall I vent it all out,
星に
to the stars?
エリクサーに張り替える作業もなんとなくなんだ
Restringing with Elixirs feels somehow aimless too.
欠けた爪を少し触る
I touch my chipped nail a little.
半径300mmの体で必死に鳴いてる
Crying out desperately with a body of 300mm radius.
音楽にとっちゃここが地球だな
For music, this is the Earth.
空気を握って空を殴るよ
I grasp the air and punch the sky.
何にも起きない私は無力さ
Nothing happens, I am powerless.
だけどさその手でこの鉄を弾いたら
But if I strum these steel strings with that hand,
何かが変わって見えた
something looked different.
ような
It seemed.
眩しい眩しいそんなに光るなよ
So bright, so bright, don't shine so much.
影がより色濃くなってしまうだろう
The shadows will probably become darker
なんでこんな熱くなっちゃってんだと
Wondering why it's gotten so hot
曼梅
Manmai
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
I, the fool, just sing
うるさいんだって心臓
My heart is noisy
青い惑星ひとりぼっち
All alone on this blue planet
いっぱいの音を聞いてきた
I've listened to so many sounds
回り続けていく
Continuing to spin around
億年
For a hundred million years
一瞬でもいいから
Even just a moment is fine
聞いて
Listen
聞けよ
Listen!
私
I
私はここにいる
I am here
殴り書きみたいな音
A sound like a scribble
出せない状態で叫んだよ
I shouted it out without letting it out
なんかなりたいなりたい
I feel like I want to become, want to become
何者かでいい
Just being someone is fine
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
I, the fool, just sing
ぶちまけちゃおうか
Shall I just dump it all out
星に
To the stars
はーい！ねね先輩お誕生日...
Yaaay! Nene-senpai, happy birth...
おめでとうございます！
...day to you!
あーありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
イェイイェイイェイイェイ！
Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
イェイイェイイェイ！
Yeah yeah yeah!
というわけで、ReGLOSSから奏ちゃんに来てもらいました！
So, we had Kanade-chan come from ReGLOSS!
イェーイ！音乃瀬奏です！
Yaaaay! I'm Otonose Kanade!
お願いしたよー！
Thanks for coming!
イェーイ！
Yaaay!
今回はね、ねねね、普段の奏ちゃんとの喋りと歌のギャップが大好きで
This time, see, Nene really loves the gap between Kanade-chan's usual talking and her singing
はぁ！
Haa!
そう普段これじゃん
Right, usually she's like this.
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
あっ、えっ、嬉しい...
Ah, eh, I'm happy...
普段これだけど歌うと急にね、なんか切ない、エモいみたいな
Usually she's like this, but when she sings, suddenly it's like, painful, emo-ish.
あー、えー...
Ah, eh...
うーるーしー
I'm so hap-py-
ねね先輩にそう言ってもらえるととっても嬉しいです！
I'm so happy to have Nene-senpai say that!
本当？
Really?
はい！
Yes!
そのイメージがめっちゃ好きで、一緒になんかそういうちょっとギャップが出る曲歌いたいなと思って
I really like that image, so I thought I wanted to sing a song where that kind of gap comes out a bit together.
ねね先輩もめっちゃかっこよかったです！
Nene-senpai was also super cool!
ありがとう
Thanks
サンキュー！
Thank you!
ィエーイ！
Yaaay!
あとなんか髪の毛の色もさ
Also, the hair color...
確かに！同じ金髪...
That's true! From the same blonde...
黄色から
From yellow...
グラデーション！
Gradient!
ピンク
Pink.
オレンジ
Orange.
そう！
Right!
そんな親和性あるかなと思って、オファーしてみました
I thought there might be some synergy like that, so I offered.
受けてくれてありがとう
Thanks for accepting.
こちらこそありがとうございます！
Thank you!
一緒に歌えてとっても嬉しかったです！
I was very happy to sing together!
奏ちゃんのね、ダンスの覚え方が可愛いんだよ
Kanade-chan's way of remembering the dance is cute.
えっ、そうですか？
Eh, is it?
なんか、忍者忍者
Like, ninja ninja...
忍者忍者忍者...って
...ninja ninja ninja...
こっち向いて、こうなってて、こう忍者...
Face this way, it goes like this, like this ninja...
覚える...覚え方
To remember... the way to remember
ありますよね
You have one right
先生たちもめっちゃ笑顔だったよ
The teachers were all smiling too.
えーとじゃあ、最後に...
Um, well then, lastly...
ちょっとどうしようかな
What should we do
ギャップのある感じで、スクショ...
A screenshot time with a 'gap' feel...
タイム！
Time!
任せてください！
Leave it to me!
任せてくださいなの？
'Leave it to me', huh?
はい！
Yes!
ちょっといけるかな
Can I do it?
ねねも
Nene too.
ちょっとかっこいい、エモい感じで
A bit cool, emo feel.
任せてください
Leave it to me.
いきますよ
Here we go.
いこう
Let's go.
おほっ...
Oho...
おと...
Sound...
え？今なんて、何やった今？
Eh? Just now what... what did you do just now?
ちょっとかっこいいエモい感じで
A bit cool emo feel
おお...
Oh...
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms bloom
見慣れたいつもの
On the usual familiar
坂道に
Slope
あーあー別れを
Ah, signaling a parting
泣いて笑った
Those days we cried and laughed
あの日々
Those days
なんだか昨日のことのよう
Somehow feel like yesterday
この道はそう
I felt like this road
未来へ続く道
continues on to the future
そんな気がしたの
or at least that's how it seemed.
例年より早い開花予想を
The forecast for an earlier bloom than usual,
君は嬉しがってた
you seemed so happy about it.
私は笑って そうだねって言った
I laughed and said, "Yeah, you're right."
あと少ししたらもうここには戻れないのに
Even though I won't be able to come back here soon.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
Feelings that I can't express well with words,
君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて
if I were to confess them to you,
伝えよう
what should I say?
最初で最後
For the first and last time.
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The road we walked home together that day,
私にとって特別な思い出
is a special memory for me.
忘れないよ
I won't forget it.
さよならメモリーズ
Goodbye memories.
春が来たら
When spring comes,
それぞれの道を
we'll go our separate ways.
また会える日を願って
Hoping for the day we can meet again,
さよなら
goodbye.
小さくつぶやいた
I whispered softly.
空はあの頃と変わらず
The sky is unchanged from back then,
青くて
so blue,
だからちょっと泣けた
that it made me cry a little.
わざと遠回りしたの
I took the long way on purpose.
少しでも長く君の隣にいたくて
Because I wanted to be by your side just a little longer.
私はおどけて
I joked around,
まちがえたって言った
and said I made a mistake.
君が笑うその顔が
Your smiling face
眩しくて目を逸らした
was so dazzling I looked away.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
Feelings that I can't express well with words,
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
I walked this path holding them in my heart.
覚えてる
I remember.
あの時君は私の名前を呼んでくれた
That time, you called my name.
二人夕暮れの帰り道で
On our way home at twilight, the two of us.
忘れないよ
I won't forget.
さよならメモリーズ
Goodbye memories.
出会えたこと
The fact that we met,
感謝してる
I'm grateful for it.
初めて見た
The first time we saw
満開の桜
the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
あれからどれくらい
Since then, how much...
変われたんだろう
I wonder how much I've changed.
一目見た時に思ったんだ
I thought so the moment I saw you,
この人のこと好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall in love with this person."
なんでかな
I wonder why?
わかんないよ
I don't know.
それからの毎日はとても楽しくて
Every day since then has been so much fun,
だけど同じくらいに辛かったんだ
but it was just as painful.
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't find the right words.
だから私 君となんていうか
So I... with you... how should I put it...
今のまま さよならしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye like this.
友達のままじゃ もう嫌なの
I don't want to just be friends anymore.
言おうと思っていた
I was going to tell you.
私 君の
I... about you...
君のことずっと
about you, for a long time...
ずっと前から好きでした
I've loved you for a long time!
やっと言えた
I finally said it.
いつだって君は笑われ者だ
You are always the laughingstock.
やることなすことついてなくて
Nothing you do ever goes right.
揚げ句に雨に降られ
And to top it off, you get rained on.
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella gets blown away by the wind.
そこのノラはご苦労様と足を踏んづけてった
The stray dog there says "Good job" and steps on your foot.
いつも通り君は嫌われ者だ
As always, you are the hated one.
何にもせずとも遠ざけられて
Pushed away without even doing anything.
努力をしてみるけど
You try to make an effort, but...
その理由なんてなんとなくで
The reason is just "somehow."
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
You were at a loss and grieving.
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
Then you should just use my voice.
人によっては理解不能で
Some people won't understand it,
なんて耳障りひどい声だって
Saying "What a harsh, terrible voice."
言われるけど
They might say that, but...
きっと君の力になれる
I'm sure I can be your strength.
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So please, try making me sing.
そう君の
Yes, with your...
君だけの言葉でさ
With your own words, only yours.
綴って連ねて
Spell them out, string them together.
あたしがその言葉を叫ぶから
Because I will shout those words for you.
描いて理想を
Draw your ideals.
その想いは誰にも触れさせない
I won't let anyone touch those feelings.
ガラクタの声はそして響く
And so the junk voice resonates.
ありのままを不器用に繋いで
Clumsily connecting things just as they are.
精一杯に
With all its might,
大声を上げる
Raising a loud voice.
いつからか君は人気者だ
Since when did you become popular?
たくさんの人にもてはやされ
Praised by so many people.
あたしも鼻が高い
I am proud too.
でもいつからか君は変わった
But since when did you change?
冷たくなって
You became cold.
だけど寂しそうだった
But you looked lonely.
もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
"I've had enough of this machine voice."
僕は僕自身なんだよって
"I am myself," you said.
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
Finally, you couldn't hold it back anymore,
あたしを嫌った
And hated me.
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Someone behind you says,
虎の威を借る狐のくせに
"Even though you're just a fox borrowing the tiger's power."
ねえ君は
Hey, you...
一人で泣いてたんだね
You were crying all alone, weren't you?
聴こえる？この声
Can you hear? This voice.
あたしがその言葉をかき消すから
Because I will erase those words.
わかってる？本当は
Do you understand? Actually,
君が誰より優しいってことを
That you are kinder than anyone else.
ガラクタの声はそして歌った
And so the junk voice sang.
他の誰でもない君のために
For you, and no one else.
きしんでいく限界を超えて
Creaking, going beyond the limit.
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を思いついたことだろう
How many words must the two of us have thought of?
だけど今は何ひとつ思いつかなくて
But now, I can't think of a single one.
だけど何もかもわかった
But I understood everything.
そうか、きっとこれは夢だ
I see, surely this is a dream.
永遠に覚めない君と会えた
One I'll never wake up from, where I met you.
そんな夢
Such a dream.
ガラクタは幸せそうな顔をしたまま
The junk, with a happy look on its face,
どれだけ呼んでももう動かない
No matter how much you call, it won't move anymore.
望んだはずの結末に
At the ending you were supposed to have wished for,
君は泣き叫ぶ
You cry and scream.
嘘だろ嘘だろってそう泣き叫ぶ
"It's a lie, it's a lie," you cry and scream.
僕は無力だ
I am powerless.
ガラクタ一つだって救えやしない
I can't even save a single piece of junk.
想いは涙に
My feelings turn to tears...
ポツリポツリとその頬濡らす
Trickling, trickling, wetting those cheeks
その時 世界は 途端にその色を
At that moment, the world instantly changes its color
大きく変える
Drastically
悲しみ 喜び
Sadness, joy
全てを一人とひとつは知った
Everyone learned that all is one and one is all
言葉は歌になりこの世界を 再び駆け巡る君のために
Words become song and race through this world again, for your sake
その声に 意志を宿して
Imbuing that voice with will
今 思いが響く
Now, feelings resonate
あーいポルカがハモリじゃないよみんな
Yeees, that wasn't Polka harmonizing, everyone!
ねねの声だよ
That was Nene's voice!
というわけで、えーっと ゲストにいっぱいきてもらって
So, um... we had lots of guests come over,
いっぱいいろんな歌歌えて楽しかったです
and I had fun singing lots of different songs.
ちなみにフレンズはママのチョイスです
By the way, "Friends" was Mama's choice.
みんなママのチョイスかなって言ってたから大正解です
Everyone was asking if it was Mama's choice, so you're absolutely correct!
じゃあ告知いきたいと思います
Now, let's go to the announcements.
まずはこちら
First is this!
桃鈴ねね誕生日記念2026 グッズが発売されます
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise will be on sale!
まずはこちら
First up is this.
ワイドラバーマット
Wide Rubber Mat.
上目遣いでねねがね 上を見ながらみんなにお願いってしてる感じのイラストで
It's an illustration of Nene looking up at you, pleading "Please?"
イラストはまるる先生書き下ろしで
The illustration is newly drawn by Maruru-sensei.
横幅がめっちゃ広いので
It's really wide, so...
キーボードとかマウス置いてデスクで使ってください
please put your keyboard and mouse on it and use it at your desk.
そして次はこちら
And next is this.
Tシャツ
T-shirt.
さっきのね、同じキービジュアルを使った 前面はTシャツ
It uses the same key visual as before. The front has the design...
後ろ面は尊き桃鈴って書いてあるTシャツです
and the back is a T-shirt with "Precious Momosuzu" written on it.
前出した「やっぱり桃鈴」に続く
Continuing from the "Momosuzu After All" I released before,
「尊き桃鈴」のTシャツが出来上がりました
the "Precious Momosuzu" T-shirt is complete!
これもぜひ着てください
Please wear this one too.
尊いかやっぱりか選んでください
Choose between "Precious" or "After All".
そして次はこちら
And next is this.
ランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー
Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keyholder.
いろんな衣装のねねがね可愛いポーズをしています
Nene is striking cute poses in various outfits.
イラストは花杜ゆのき先生に書いてもらいました
The illustrations were drawn by Hanamori Yunoki-sensei.
台座とボールチェーンがついてるので
Since it comes with a base and a ball chain,
ミニアクスタとしても使えるし
you can use it as a mini acrylic stand,
キーホルダーとしても使えます
or as a keyholder.
そして次 こちら
And next, this.
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー 私服衣装ver.
Plushie Keyholder Casual Outfit version.
これめっちゃこだわって作ってて
I was super particular about making this,
もう可愛さ全振りの ねねね 私服衣装のぬいぐるみのキーホルダーになります
It's a plushie keyholder of Nene in casual clothes, fully maxed out on cuteness.
ボールチェーン付きなのでカバンとかにつけて一緒にお出かけしてほしいな
It has a ball chain, so I want you to attach it to your bag and go out together.
前のね 前髪とか顔とかすごいこだわって作ったので
I was really particular about the bangs and face,
絶対可愛い自信あるので
so I'm confident it's absolutely cute.
実物今度見せたいと思います
I want to show you the real thing next time.
そしてラスト
And lastly...
ボイスです
it's the Voice.
君とねねのお誕生日
"You and Nene's Birthday."
ねねがね みんなのお誕生日も祝ってあげたいと思います
Nene wants to celebrate everyone's birthday too.
しょうがないので
Since I guess I have to...
今すぐ聞いてもいいし自分の誕生日に聞いてもよし
You can listen to it right now, or listen to it on your birthday, that's fine too!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら
And the Full Set Purchase Bonus is this.
数量限定は直筆サインと
The Limited Quantity version comes with a hand-written signature and...
複製の箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード
a postcard with a foil-stamped reproduced message.
そして通常盤は
And the Regular Edition...
箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入っています
contains a foil-stamped reproduced signature and message.
数量限定盤今回あるので皆さんよろしくお願いします
There is a Limited Quantity version this time, so please check it out everyone.
さらにボイスもついてきます
Plus, the Voice also comes with it.
タイトル
Title:
「毎日一番に見てほしいの」ってことで
With "I want you to look at me first every day,"
幼馴染のねねがね みんなに行こうぜ行こうぜって
your childhood friend Nene is like "Let's go! Let's go!" to everyone,
朝から乗っかかってくるシチュエーションボイスあります
in a situation voice where she jumps on you from the morning.
特典もたくさんあるのでぜひフルセットで買ってください
There are lots of bonuses, so please buy the full set.
このあと21時30分から販売開始です
Sales start after this at 21:30.
よろしくお願いします
Thank you!
そして
And then...
オリ曲のMVが出ます
the MV for my original song is coming out!
Liminal
本日MVは21時15分からを予定しています
The MV is scheduled for today at 21:15.
リリースは3月3日の0時から
Release is from 0:00 on March 3rd.
よろしくお願いします
Please check it out.
どんな曲だろうね
I wonder what kind of song it is?
今回のライブのタイトルにもなってます
It's also the title of this live concert.
そして 超重大告知があります
And, I have a Super Important Announcement!
こちら
This!
Peachful Story
桃鈴ねねの1stアルバムが
Momosuzu Nene's 1st Album...
このあと21時...あ、今？ちょうど今？
after this at 21:00... Ah, now? Right now?
21時から始まりました イェーイ
Started at 21:00! Yaaay!
初回盤と通常盤2種類あります
There are two types: First Press Edition and Regular Edition.
通常盤はこちら
The Regular Edition is this.
りいちゅ先生が描いてくれた通常盤のやつと
The Regular Edition drawn by Riichu-sensei, and...
ランダムのアナザージャケットがついてきます
a Random Another Jacket comes with it.
なんとこちら ドン
Surprise, this! Bam!
いなちゃんとラオーラちゃんに描いてもらいました
Ina-chan and Raora-chan drew them for me!
マイク持ってる方がいなちゃんで
The one holding the mic is Ina-chan,
踊ってる方がラオーラちゃんが描いてくれました
and Raora-chan drew the one dancing.
ありがとう
Thank you!
こちらは数量限定で直筆サインが入っているので
This one has a hand-written signature in limited quantities, so...
みなさんぜひチェックしてください
everyone, please check it out!
リバーシブル仕様の直筆サイン入りアナザージャケット
A reversible handwritten signed another jacket.
どっちをね、表にして主役にしてもいいですし
You can make either side the front and the main feature,
なんなら2個買っていただいて
or if you like, please buy two copies,
両方ともおもて面にして
display both as the front side,
ねねとねねをがっちゃんこさせてください
and combine Nene and Nene together.
そして、こちらがついてきます
And, this also comes with it.
レコーディングブックと、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの
A recording book, and a Hololive Official Card Game
カードもついてきます
card are also included.
ねねのね、どんな感じで歌ってたとか
Like how Nene was singing,
ここ怒られたとか
or where I got scolded,
そういうのがまとまったノートになってまーす
that kind of thing is compiled into a notebook.
そして、もう一つあります！
And, there is one more thing!
なんと、こちら！
Check this out!
「ねねねのね！」ねねのファーストEP
"Nenenene!" Nene's first EP,
グッズとして出したね、ねねのCDが
Nene's CD that was released as merchandise,
復刻になります！
is being reissued!
イェーイ！
Yay!
これね、あの意外と多分持ってる人すく...少ないんじゃないかなと思います
This one, surprisingly, probably f... few people have it, I think.
あの、今までのねねのね、あの有名な曲たちが入っていますので
Um, it contains Nene's famous songs from before,
こちらの復刻版もぜひ聴いて
so please listen to this reissue version too,
今回のアルバムと一緒に
together with this album,
全曲聴いて、覚えて
listen to all the songs, remember them,
ほしいなって思います！
and I hope you enjoy them!
さて、さっきLiminalのMVの告知をしたと思うんですけど
Well then, I think I announced the Liminal MV earlier,
どんな曲か聴きたいよねみんな
everyone wants to hear what kind of song it is, right?
それじゃあねね、今からしっとりとやっていこうかなと思います
So then, Nene is going to perform it calmly now.
それでは聴いてください
Please listen.
Liminal
見つめる
Staring
くすんだ瞳で
with dull eyes,
光を探して迷ってた
I was lost searching for the light.
いくつもの痛みに
Bound by
縛られたまま
countless pains,
頬を伝う
it runs down my cheek.
画面に
Why does
映る私はどうして
the me reflected on the screen
涙の跡が消されているんだろう
have the tear tracks erased?
ひび割れた
Beyond the
硝子の向こう
cracked glass,
笑って繕っていた
I was patching things up with a smile.
誰かが言った
Someone said,
「偽物みたいだ」
"You look like a fake."
「ただの影だ」って
"Just a shadow,"
決めつけたけど
they decided arbitrarily, but...
まやかしじゃなくて
It's not a deception.
私が私で
The reason why I
いる理由を
am myself,
君の笑顔に
I was receiving it
貰っていた
from your smile.
そうさ
That's right,
画面の中
inside the screen.
隠せない 消えない 見えない それでも
Can't hide, can't erase, can't see, even so,
それでも
even so,
私は
I...
君の光を追って
Chasing your light,
閉じこもる暗い硝子の曇りを払って
clearing the fog from the dark glass I shut myself in.
今 明日を見つけたんだ
Now, I've found tomorrow.
忘れたくない
I don't want to forget,
君がくれたこの感情を
this emotion you gave me.
見つめる
Staring at
姿 鏡の奥の
the figure deep in the mirror.
涙の跡は見せられないけど
I can't show the tear tracks, but...
磨かれた
Beyond the
硝子の向こう
polished glass,
笑って輝いていたいだけで
I just want to smile and shine.
「誰のためだっけ」
"For whose sake was it?"
声が 姿が
My voice, my form...
誰でもない気がした
I felt like I was no one.
「孤独だ」って
"I'm alone,"
また迷い出す
I start to get lost again.
画面の奥の瞳を
At the eyes deep in the screen,
いつでも
always,
いつでも 君は
always, you...
映す光の中に
Inside the light that reflects,
名もない私の声を見つけてくれてた
you were finding my nameless voice.
ずっと
Always.
この声も 姿も
This voice, and this form too,
紛れもない私だ
is unmistakably me.
この声も、姿も、
This voice, and this form,
ありのままでいいんだ
It's okay to be just as I am.
この気持ちは本物だ
This feeling is real.
縛られても
Even if I'm tied down,
触れられなくても
Even if I can't be touched.
君が示してくれてたから
Because you showed me the way.
いつかこの「私」で
Someday, as this "me",
ずっと光を手繰って
I'll keep pulling in the light.
きっと見つけ出す
I'll surely find it,
誰でもない「君」に会えるまで
Until I can meet the "you" who is no one else.
境界線はすぐそこに
The boundary line is right there.
そう
Yes,
画面の向こう
beyond the screen.
繋ぎたい
I want to connect,
越えたい
I want to cross over,
触れたい
I want to touch,
それこそ
that is...
それこそ私なんだ
That is exactly who I am.
「君」と光になって
Becoming light with "you",
未だ遮る硝子の壁の先まで
To beyond the glass wall that still blocks us.
届くように笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling so it reaches you.
迷いはない
There is no hesitation.
君がくれたこの感情と
With this emotion you gave me.
あー
Ah-